<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nixie Clock Part II</title>
      <link>http://example.org/nixie-clock-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/nixie-clock-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>A long time in a galaxy far far away there was an unfinished project that was sitting on a table just waiting to be completed.
What works:
High Voltage Power supply
Nixie Tubes
What doesn’t:
Software
Case
Wanted Features:
Automatic time setting via a timeserver
USB-C power supply
Dimming during night time
Frequent cycling of all numbers in order to reduce wear and tear
On the software side the wlan capabilities of the esp32 muc is used, which enables the connection to a timeserver for accurate timekeeping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring the air</title>
      <link>http://example.org/monitoring-the-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/monitoring-the-air/</guid>
      <description>Indoor air quality - you probably never taught about this, but it&amp;rsquo;s just as, if not more important than outdoor air quality, since most people spend more than half of their day indoors. So how is the air?
Quick Note: You can find this projects code and documentation on Github!
Well, lets quantify it: CO2 is the most important short-term indicator, its measured in ppm parts-per-million. If the level is too high you can&amp;rsquo;t concentrate at first and then get dizzy and sleepy:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nixie clock Part I</title>
      <link>http://example.org/nixie-clock-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/nixie-clock-part-i/</guid>
      <description>One might know them from the bomb-defusing scene in the Bond movie &amp;ldquo;Goldfinger&amp;rdquo; or the Divergence Meter from Steins;Gate.
In short, its ten(0-9) wires glowing neon yellow in a vacuum tube, first replaced by seven-segment displays, they are becoming increasingly popular nowadays, because of their beauty.
There are quite a lot of kits available online, but there is the fun in buying one?
Designing the Circuit: The difficulty in it lies in the operating voltage of a Nixie-clock: ~170V</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Butchers´ Menu</title>
      <link>http://example.org/project-loca/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/project-loca/</guid>
      <description>So as most of you during the Pandemic, studying or working from home, I and especially my neighbors struggled with eating a healthy meal every day, since they were used to the canteen at work and hadn&amp;rsquo;t had the time to cook each day.
So as most of you during the Pandemic, studying or working from home, I and especially my neighbors struggled with eating a healthy meal every day, since they were used to the canteen at work and hadn&amp;rsquo;t had the time to cook each day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://example.org/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2003 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/info/</guid>
      <description>I'm a 22 year old student currently pursuing my master's at TUM in Munich. I did my bachelor's at Friedrich-Alexander-Universität Erlangen-Nürnberg with a little excursion to Royal Melbourne Institute of Technology.

My interests include FPGAs, chip design and testing. This site shows a few old projects from the early years of my studies.

</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
